{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685108504","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685108504"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" df0e5ab9-a820-4ace-b28a-cc1968a0bca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaitwa Bi Simu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAITWA"," userResponse":" ANAITWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685108808","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685108808"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" df0e5ab9-a820-4ace-b28a-cc1968a0bca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaitwa Bi Simu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BI"," userResponse":" BI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685109411","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685109411"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" df0e5ab9-a820-4ace-b28a-cc1968a0bca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaitwa Bi Simu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMU"," userResponse":" SIMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685112440","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685112439"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" df0e5ab9-a820-4ace-b28a-cc1968a0bca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwangalie!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANGALIE"," userResponse":" MWANGALIE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685115351","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685115350"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" df0e5ab9-a820-4ace-b28a-cc1968a0bca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akiamka anazipanga simu zake tano juu ya meza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANA"," userResponse":" ANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685115993","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685115992"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" df0e5ab9-a820-4ace-b28a-cc1968a0bca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akiamka anazipanga simu zake tano juu ya meza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMU"," userResponse":" SIMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685116753","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685116751"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" df0e5ab9-a820-4ace-b28a-cc1968a0bca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akiamka anazipanga simu zake tano juu ya meza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANO"," userResponse":" TANO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685119820","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685119819"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" df0e5ab9-a820-4ace-b28a-cc1968a0bca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akiamka anazipanga simu zake tano juu ya meza."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKIAMKA"," userResponse":" AKIAMKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685121389","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685121389"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" df0e5ab9-a820-4ace-b28a-cc1968a0bca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akiamka anazipanga simu zake tano juu ya meza."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAZIPANGA"," userResponse":" ANAZIPANGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685121984","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685121983"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" df0e5ab9-a820-4ace-b28a-cc1968a0bca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akiamka anazipanga simu zake tano juu ya meza."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMU"," userResponse":" SIMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685122648","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685122648"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" df0e5ab9-a820-4ace-b28a-cc1968a0bca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akiamka anazipanga simu zake tano juu ya meza."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAKE"," userResponse":" ZAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685123510","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685123510"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" df0e5ab9-a820-4ace-b28a-cc1968a0bca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akiamka anazipanga simu zake tano juu ya meza."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANO"," userResponse":" TANO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685124425","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685124425"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" df0e5ab9-a820-4ace-b28a-cc1968a0bca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akiamka anazipanga simu zake tano juu ya meza."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUU"," userResponse":" JUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685124551","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685124550"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" df0e5ab9-a820-4ace-b28a-cc1968a0bca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akiamka anazipanga simu zake tano juu ya meza."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685125075","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685125074"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" df0e5ab9-a820-4ace-b28a-cc1968a0bca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akiamka anazipanga simu zake tano juu ya meza."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MEZA"," userResponse":" MEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685127849","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685127848"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" df0e5ab9-a820-4ace-b28a-cc1968a0bca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya manjano ni ya kuwasiliana na watu wa familia yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685128783","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685128782"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" df0e5ab9-a820-4ace-b28a-cc1968a0bca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya manjano ni ya kuwasiliana na watu wa familia yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANJANO"," userResponse":" MANJANO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685129194","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685129193"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" df0e5ab9-a820-4ace-b28a-cc1968a0bca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya manjano ni ya kuwasiliana na watu wa familia yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685129298","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685129297"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" df0e5ab9-a820-4ace-b28a-cc1968a0bca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya manjano ni ya kuwasiliana na watu wa familia yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685130437","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685130436"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" df0e5ab9-a820-4ace-b28a-cc1968a0bca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya manjano ni ya kuwasiliana na watu wa familia yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWASILIANA"," userResponse":" KUWASILIANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685130675","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685130674"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" df0e5ab9-a820-4ace-b28a-cc1968a0bca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya manjano ni ya kuwasiliana na watu wa familia yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685131191","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685131191"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" df0e5ab9-a820-4ace-b28a-cc1968a0bca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya manjano ni ya kuwasiliana na watu wa familia yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATU"," userResponse":" WATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685131449","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685131448"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" df0e5ab9-a820-4ace-b28a-cc1968a0bca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya manjano ni ya kuwasiliana na watu wa familia yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685132334","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685132333"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" df0e5ab9-a820-4ace-b28a-cc1968a0bca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya manjano ni ya kuwasiliana na watu wa familia yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FAMILIA"," userResponse":" FAMILIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685132827","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685132827"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" df0e5ab9-a820-4ace-b28a-cc1968a0bca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya manjano ni ya kuwasiliana na watu wa familia yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685135609","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685135608"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" df0e5ab9-a820-4ace-b28a-cc1968a0bca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ile nyeupe ni ya kuwasiliana na wenzake kazini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILE"," userResponse":" ILE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685136502","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685136502"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" df0e5ab9-a820-4ace-b28a-cc1968a0bca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ile nyeupe ni ya kuwasiliana na wenzake kazini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYEUPE"," userResponse":" NYEUPE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685136984","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685136984"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" df0e5ab9-a820-4ace-b28a-cc1968a0bca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ile nyeupe ni ya kuwasiliana na wenzake kazini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685137088","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685137088"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" df0e5ab9-a820-4ace-b28a-cc1968a0bca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ile nyeupe ni ya kuwasiliana na wenzake kazini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685138106","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685138105"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" df0e5ab9-a820-4ace-b28a-cc1968a0bca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ile nyeupe ni ya kuwasiliana na wenzake kazini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWASILIANA"," userResponse":" KUWASILIANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685138366","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685138366"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" df0e5ab9-a820-4ace-b28a-cc1968a0bca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ile nyeupe ni ya kuwasiliana na wenzake kazini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685139040","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685139040"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" df0e5ab9-a820-4ace-b28a-cc1968a0bca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ile nyeupe ni ya kuwasiliana na wenzake kazini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENZAKE"," userResponse":" WENZAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685139894","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685139894"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" df0e5ab9-a820-4ace-b28a-cc1968a0bca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ile nyeupe ni ya kuwasiliana na wenzake kazini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAZINI"," userResponse":" KAZINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685142905","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685142904"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" df0e5ab9-a820-4ace-b28a-cc1968a0bca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bali ile nyekundu ni ya kuwasiliana na wale walio na madeni yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BALI"," userResponse":" BALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685143206","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685143206"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" df0e5ab9-a820-4ace-b28a-cc1968a0bca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bali ile nyekundu ni ya kuwasiliana na wale walio na madeni yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILE"," userResponse":" ILE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685143952","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685143952"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" df0e5ab9-a820-4ace-b28a-cc1968a0bca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bali ile nyekundu ni ya kuwasiliana na wale walio na madeni yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYEKUNDU"," userResponse":" NYEKUNDU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685144248","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685144247"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" df0e5ab9-a820-4ace-b28a-cc1968a0bca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bali ile nyekundu ni ya kuwasiliana na wale walio na madeni yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685144335","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685144335"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" df0e5ab9-a820-4ace-b28a-cc1968a0bca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bali ile nyekundu ni ya kuwasiliana na wale walio na madeni yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685145419","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685145419"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" df0e5ab9-a820-4ace-b28a-cc1968a0bca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bali ile nyekundu ni ya kuwasiliana na wale walio na madeni yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWASILIANA"," userResponse":" KUWASILIANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685145669","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685145668"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" df0e5ab9-a820-4ace-b28a-cc1968a0bca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bali ile nyekundu ni ya kuwasiliana na wale walio na madeni yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685146304","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685146303"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" df0e5ab9-a820-4ace-b28a-cc1968a0bca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bali ile nyekundu ni ya kuwasiliana na wale walio na madeni yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALE"," userResponse":" WALE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685147362","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685147362"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" df0e5ab9-a820-4ace-b28a-cc1968a0bca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bali ile nyekundu ni ya kuwasiliana na wale walio na madeni yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIO"," userResponse":" WALIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685147530","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685147530"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" df0e5ab9-a820-4ace-b28a-cc1968a0bca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bali ile nyekundu ni ya kuwasiliana na wale walio na madeni yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685148300","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685148299"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" df0e5ab9-a820-4ace-b28a-cc1968a0bca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bali ile nyekundu ni ya kuwasiliana na wale walio na madeni yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MADENI"," userResponse":" MADENI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685148799","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685148798"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" df0e5ab9-a820-4ace-b28a-cc1968a0bca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bali ile nyekundu ni ya kuwasiliana na wale walio na madeni yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685151828","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685151828"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" df0e5ab9-a820-4ace-b28a-cc1968a0bca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nayo ile ya waridi ni ya kuwasiliana na marafiki zake wa dhati."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAYO"," userResponse":" NAYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685152372","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685152372"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" df0e5ab9-a820-4ace-b28a-cc1968a0bca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nayo ile ya waridi ni ya kuwasiliana na marafiki zake wa dhati."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILE"," userResponse":" ILE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685152434","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685152434"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" df0e5ab9-a820-4ace-b28a-cc1968a0bca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nayo ile ya waridi ni ya kuwasiliana na marafiki zake wa dhati."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685153298","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685153298"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" df0e5ab9-a820-4ace-b28a-cc1968a0bca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nayo ile ya waridi ni ya kuwasiliana na marafiki zake wa dhati."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WARIDI"," userResponse":" WARIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685153701","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685153701"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" df0e5ab9-a820-4ace-b28a-cc1968a0bca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nayo ile ya waridi ni ya kuwasiliana na marafiki zake wa dhati."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685153785","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685153784"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" df0e5ab9-a820-4ace-b28a-cc1968a0bca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nayo ile ya waridi ni ya kuwasiliana na marafiki zake wa dhati."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685154780","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685154780"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" df0e5ab9-a820-4ace-b28a-cc1968a0bca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nayo ile ya waridi ni ya kuwasiliana na marafiki zake wa dhati."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWASILIANA"," userResponse":" KUWASILIANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685154980","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685154980"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" df0e5ab9-a820-4ace-b28a-cc1968a0bca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nayo ile ya waridi ni ya kuwasiliana na marafiki zake wa dhati."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685155685","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685155685"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" df0e5ab9-a820-4ace-b28a-cc1968a0bca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nayo ile ya waridi ni ya kuwasiliana na marafiki zake wa dhati."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MARAFIKI"," userResponse":" MARAFIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685156208","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685156207"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" df0e5ab9-a820-4ace-b28a-cc1968a0bca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nayo ile ya waridi ni ya kuwasiliana na marafiki zake wa dhati."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAKE"," userResponse":" ZAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685156401","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685156401"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" df0e5ab9-a820-4ace-b28a-cc1968a0bca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nayo ile ya waridi ni ya kuwasiliana na marafiki zake wa dhati."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685157176","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685157176"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" df0e5ab9-a820-4ace-b28a-cc1968a0bca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nayo ile ya waridi ni ya kuwasiliana na marafiki zake wa dhati."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DHATI"," userResponse":" DHATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685160155","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685160155"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" df0e5ab9-a820-4ace-b28a-cc1968a0bca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ile ya kizambarau anaitumia kuwasiliana na watu wanaohitaji msaada wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILE"," userResponse":" ILE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685160252","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685160252"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" df0e5ab9-a820-4ace-b28a-cc1968a0bca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ile ya kizambarau anaitumia kuwasiliana na watu wanaohitaji msaada wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685161271","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685161271"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" df0e5ab9-a820-4ace-b28a-cc1968a0bca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ile ya kizambarau anaitumia kuwasiliana na watu wanaohitaji msaada wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIZAMBARAU"," userResponse":" KIZAMBARAU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685162895","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685162895"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" df0e5ab9-a820-4ace-b28a-cc1968a0bca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ile ya kizambarau anaitumia kuwasiliana na watu wanaohitaji msaada wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAITUMIA"," userResponse":" ANAITUMIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685164215","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685164215"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" df0e5ab9-a820-4ace-b28a-cc1968a0bca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ile ya kizambarau anaitumia kuwasiliana na watu wanaohitaji msaada wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWASILIANA"," userResponse":" KUWASILIANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685164673","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685164672"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" df0e5ab9-a820-4ace-b28a-cc1968a0bca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ile ya kizambarau anaitumia kuwasiliana na watu wanaohitaji msaada wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685165129","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685165128"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" df0e5ab9-a820-4ace-b28a-cc1968a0bca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ile ya kizambarau anaitumia kuwasiliana na watu wanaohitaji msaada wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATU"," userResponse":" WATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685166297","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685166296"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" df0e5ab9-a820-4ace-b28a-cc1968a0bca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ile ya kizambarau anaitumia kuwasiliana na watu wanaohitaji msaada wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANAOHITAJI"," userResponse":" WANAOHITAJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685166990","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685166989"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" df0e5ab9-a820-4ace-b28a-cc1968a0bca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ile ya kizambarau anaitumia kuwasiliana na watu wanaohitaji msaada wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSAADA"," userResponse":" MSAADA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685167566","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685167565"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" df0e5ab9-a820-4ace-b28a-cc1968a0bca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ile ya kizambarau anaitumia kuwasiliana na watu wanaohitaji msaada wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685170190","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685170189"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" df0e5ab9-a820-4ace-b28a-cc1968a0bca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bi Simu hupenda watu kufurahi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BI"," userResponse":" BI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685170882","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685170881"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" df0e5ab9-a820-4ace-b28a-cc1968a0bca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bi Simu hupenda watu kufurahi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMU"," userResponse":" SIMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685171996","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685171995"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" df0e5ab9-a820-4ace-b28a-cc1968a0bca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bi Simu hupenda watu kufurahi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUPENDA"," userResponse":" HUPENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685172682","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685172681"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" df0e5ab9-a820-4ace-b28a-cc1968a0bca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bi Simu hupenda watu kufurahi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATU"," userResponse":" WATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685174057","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685174055"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" df0e5ab9-a820-4ace-b28a-cc1968a0bca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bi Simu hupenda watu kufurahi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUFURAHI"," userResponse":" KUFURAHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685176791","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685176791"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" df0e5ab9-a820-4ace-b28a-cc1968a0bca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapendi ugomvi wala vita."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPENDI"," userResponse":" HAPENDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685177596","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685177596"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" df0e5ab9-a820-4ace-b28a-cc1968a0bca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapendi ugomvi wala vita."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UGOMVI"," userResponse":" UGOMVI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685178350","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685178349"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" df0e5ab9-a820-4ace-b28a-cc1968a0bca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapendi ugomvi wala vita."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALA"," userResponse":" WALA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685178853","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685178853"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" df0e5ab9-a820-4ace-b28a-cc1968a0bca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapendi ugomvi wala vita."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VITA"," userResponse":" VITA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685182164","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685182163"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" df0e5ab9-a820-4ace-b28a-cc1968a0bca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huwaalika watoto kuangalia runinga katika duka lake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUWAALIKA"," userResponse":" HUWAALIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685183181","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685183181"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" df0e5ab9-a820-4ace-b28a-cc1968a0bca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huwaalika watoto kuangalia runinga katika duka lake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATOTO"," userResponse":" WATOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685184272","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685184272"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" df0e5ab9-a820-4ace-b28a-cc1968a0bca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huwaalika watoto kuangalia runinga katika duka lake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUANGALIA"," userResponse":" KUANGALIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685185051","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685185051"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" df0e5ab9-a820-4ace-b28a-cc1968a0bca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huwaalika watoto kuangalia runinga katika duka lake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RUNINGA"," userResponse":" RUNINGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685185723","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685185723"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" df0e5ab9-a820-4ace-b28a-cc1968a0bca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huwaalika watoto kuangalia runinga katika duka lake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" KATIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685186139","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685186138"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" df0e5ab9-a820-4ace-b28a-cc1968a0bca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huwaalika watoto kuangalia runinga katika duka lake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DUKA"," userResponse":" DUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685186682","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685186682"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" df0e5ab9-a820-4ace-b28a-cc1968a0bca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huwaalika watoto kuangalia runinga katika duka lake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKE"," userResponse":" LAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685190225","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685190225"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" df0e5ab9-a820-4ace-b28a-cc1968a0bca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huwatembelea wagonjwa na wazee katika nyumba zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUWATEMBELEA"," userResponse":" HUWATEMBELEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685191252","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685191252"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" df0e5ab9-a820-4ace-b28a-cc1968a0bca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huwatembelea wagonjwa na wazee katika nyumba zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAGONJWA"," userResponse":" WAGONJWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685191794","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685191794"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" df0e5ab9-a820-4ace-b28a-cc1968a0bca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huwatembelea wagonjwa na wazee katika nyumba zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685192544","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685192543"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" df0e5ab9-a820-4ace-b28a-cc1968a0bca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huwatembelea wagonjwa na wazee katika nyumba zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAZEE"," userResponse":" WAZEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685193424","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685193423"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" df0e5ab9-a820-4ace-b28a-cc1968a0bca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huwatembelea wagonjwa na wazee katika nyumba zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" KATIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685193884","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685193884"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" df0e5ab9-a820-4ace-b28a-cc1968a0bca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huwatembelea wagonjwa na wazee katika nyumba zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBA"," userResponse":" NYUMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685194424","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685194424"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" df0e5ab9-a820-4ace-b28a-cc1968a0bca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huwatembelea wagonjwa na wazee katika nyumba zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAO"," userResponse":" ZAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685197402","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685197401"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" df0e5ab9-a820-4ace-b28a-cc1968a0bca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bi Simu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILA"," userResponse":" KILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685198693","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685198692"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" df0e5ab9-a820-4ace-b28a-cc1968a0bca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bi Simu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" APITAPO"," userResponse":" APITAPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685199648","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685199647"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" df0e5ab9-a820-4ace-b28a-cc1968a0bca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bi Simu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNA"," userResponse":" KUNA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685200384","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685200384"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" df0e5ab9-a820-4ace-b28a-cc1968a0bca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bi Simu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAYOWE"," userResponse":" MAYOWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685200720","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685200719"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" df0e5ab9-a820-4ace-b28a-cc1968a0bca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bi Simu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685201328","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685201328"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" df0e5ab9-a820-4ace-b28a-cc1968a0bca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bi Simu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BI"," userResponse":" BI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685202313","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685202312"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" df0e5ab9-a820-4ace-b28a-cc1968a0bca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bi Simu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMU"," userResponse":" SIMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685204460","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685204459"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" df0e5ab9-a820-4ace-b28a-cc1968a0bca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bi Simu!"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BI"," userResponse":" BI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685205362","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685205362"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" df0e5ab9-a820-4ace-b28a-cc1968a0bca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bi Simu!"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMU"," userResponse":" SIMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685208144","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685208143"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" df0e5ab9-a820-4ace-b28a-cc1968a0bca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naye hufurahia na kusema Mimi ni Bi Simu na hizi simu zangu ziangalieni!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAYE"," userResponse":" NAYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685209250","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685209250"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" df0e5ab9-a820-4ace-b28a-cc1968a0bca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naye hufurahia na kusema Mimi ni Bi Simu na hizi simu zangu ziangalieni!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUFURAHIA"," userResponse":" HUFURAHIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685209453","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685209453"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" df0e5ab9-a820-4ace-b28a-cc1968a0bca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naye hufurahia na kusema Mimi ni Bi Simu na hizi simu zangu ziangalieni!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685210128","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685210127"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" df0e5ab9-a820-4ace-b28a-cc1968a0bca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naye hufurahia na kusema Mimi ni Bi Simu na hizi simu zangu ziangalieni!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSEMA"," userResponse":" KUSEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685211719","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685211719"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" df0e5ab9-a820-4ace-b28a-cc1968a0bca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naye hufurahia na kusema Mimi ni Bi Simu na hizi simu zangu ziangalieni!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIMI"," userResponse":" MIMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685212580","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685212579"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" df0e5ab9-a820-4ace-b28a-cc1968a0bca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naye hufurahia na kusema Mimi ni Bi Simu na hizi simu zangu ziangalieni!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685212763","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685212763"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" df0e5ab9-a820-4ace-b28a-cc1968a0bca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naye hufurahia na kusema Mimi ni Bi Simu na hizi simu zangu ziangalieni!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BI"," userResponse":" BI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685213281","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685213280"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" df0e5ab9-a820-4ace-b28a-cc1968a0bca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naye hufurahia na kusema Mimi ni Bi Simu na hizi simu zangu ziangalieni!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMU"," userResponse":" SIMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685213865","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685213864"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" df0e5ab9-a820-4ace-b28a-cc1968a0bca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naye hufurahia na kusema Mimi ni Bi Simu na hizi simu zangu ziangalieni!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685214315","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685214314"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" df0e5ab9-a820-4ace-b28a-cc1968a0bca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naye hufurahia na kusema Mimi ni Bi Simu na hizi simu zangu ziangalieni!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIZI"," userResponse":" HIZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685214788","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685214788"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" df0e5ab9-a820-4ace-b28a-cc1968a0bca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naye hufurahia na kusema Mimi ni Bi Simu na hizi simu zangu ziangalieni!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMU"," userResponse":" SIMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685215552","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685215552"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" df0e5ab9-a820-4ace-b28a-cc1968a0bca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naye hufurahia na kusema Mimi ni Bi Simu na hizi simu zangu ziangalieni!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZANGU"," userResponse":" ZANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685216921","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685216921"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" df0e5ab9-a820-4ace-b28a-cc1968a0bca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naye hufurahia na kusema Mimi ni Bi Simu na hizi simu zangu ziangalieni!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZIANGALIENI"," userResponse":" ZIANGALIENI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685219226","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685219226"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" df0e5ab9-a820-4ace-b28a-cc1968a0bca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huyo ni Bi Simu na simu zake tano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUYO"," userResponse":" HUYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685219398","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685219398"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" df0e5ab9-a820-4ace-b28a-cc1968a0bca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huyo ni Bi Simu na simu zake tano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685219557","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685219557"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" df0e5ab9-a820-4ace-b28a-cc1968a0bca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huyo ni Bi Simu na simu zake tano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BI"," userResponse":" BI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685220177","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685220177"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" df0e5ab9-a820-4ace-b28a-cc1968a0bca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huyo ni Bi Simu na simu zake tano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMU"," userResponse":" SIMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685220638","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685220638"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" df0e5ab9-a820-4ace-b28a-cc1968a0bca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huyo ni Bi Simu na simu zake tano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685221161","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685221161"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" df0e5ab9-a820-4ace-b28a-cc1968a0bca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huyo ni Bi Simu na simu zake tano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMU"," userResponse":" SIMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685221651","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685221649"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" df0e5ab9-a820-4ace-b28a-cc1968a0bca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huyo ni Bi Simu na simu zake tano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAKE"," userResponse":" ZAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685222193","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685222193"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" df0e5ab9-a820-4ace-b28a-cc1968a0bca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huyo ni Bi Simu na simu zake tano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANO"," userResponse":" TANO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685224996","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685224993"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" df0e5ab9-a820-4ace-b28a-cc1968a0bca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Huyo ni Bi Simu na simu zake tano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685225121","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685225121"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" df0e5ab9-a820-4ace-b28a-cc1968a0bca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huyo ni Bi Simu na simu zake tano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANO"," userResponse":" TANO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.noShow.25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685231440","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685231440"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" df0e5ab9-a820-4ace-b28a-cc1968a0bca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Huyo ni Bi Simu na simu zake tano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.12__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685237470","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685237470"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" df0e5ab9-a820-4ace-b28a-cc1968a0bca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Huyo ni Bi Simu na simu zake tano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.noShow.25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685242921","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685242920"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" df0e5ab9-a820-4ace-b28a-cc1968a0bca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Huyo ni Bi Simu na simu zake tano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685253856","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685253856"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" 09438095-58af-4851-be8c-81c335fb0512"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_5"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na Dinasou wangu tunawaangalia ndege angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIMI"," userResponse":" MIMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685254110","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685254109"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" 09438095-58af-4851-be8c-81c335fb0512"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_5"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na Dinasou wangu tunawaangalia ndege angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685255113","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685255113"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" 09438095-58af-4851-be8c-81c335fb0512"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_5"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na Dinasou wangu tunawaangalia ndege angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DINASOU"," userResponse":" DINASOU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685255675","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685255675"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" 09438095-58af-4851-be8c-81c335fb0512"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_5"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na Dinasou wangu tunawaangalia ndege angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANGU"," userResponse":" WANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685257830","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685257830"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" 09438095-58af-4851-be8c-81c335fb0512"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_5"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na Dinasou wangu tunawaangalia ndege angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUNAWAANGALIA"," userResponse":" TUNAWAANGALIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685258457","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685258457"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" 09438095-58af-4851-be8c-81c335fb0512"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_5"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na Dinasou wangu tunawaangalia ndege angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDEGE"," userResponse":" NDEGE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685259221","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685259221"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" 09438095-58af-4851-be8c-81c335fb0512"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_5"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na Dinasou wangu tunawaangalia ndege angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGANI"," userResponse":" ANGANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685262417","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685262416"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" 09438095-58af-4851-be8c-81c335fb0512"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_5"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na Ndege wangu tunamkuta Sokwe mtini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIMI"," userResponse":" MIMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685262665","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685262664"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" 09438095-58af-4851-be8c-81c335fb0512"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_5"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na Ndege wangu tunamkuta Sokwe mtini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685263289","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685263288"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" 09438095-58af-4851-be8c-81c335fb0512"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_5"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na Ndege wangu tunamkuta Sokwe mtini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDEGE"," userResponse":" NDEGE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685263871","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685263871"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" 09438095-58af-4851-be8c-81c335fb0512"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_5"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na Ndege wangu tunamkuta Sokwe mtini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANGU"," userResponse":" WANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685265325","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685265325"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" 09438095-58af-4851-be8c-81c335fb0512"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_5"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na Ndege wangu tunamkuta Sokwe mtini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUNAMKUTA"," userResponse":" TUNAMKUTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685265899","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685265899"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" 09438095-58af-4851-be8c-81c335fb0512"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_5"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na Ndege wangu tunamkuta Sokwe mtini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SOKWE"," userResponse":" SOKWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685266719","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685266719"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" 09438095-58af-4851-be8c-81c335fb0512"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_5"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na Ndege wangu tunamkuta Sokwe mtini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTINI"," userResponse":" MTINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685269521","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685269520"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" 09438095-58af-4851-be8c-81c335fb0512"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_5"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ninacheza na Sokwe na twiga wangu milimani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIMI"," userResponse":" MIMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685270544","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685270544"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" 09438095-58af-4851-be8c-81c335fb0512"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_5"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ninacheza na Sokwe na twiga wangu milimani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINACHEZA"," userResponse":" NINACHEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685270745","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685270744"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" 09438095-58af-4851-be8c-81c335fb0512"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_5"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ninacheza na Sokwe na twiga wangu milimani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685271406","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685271405"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" 09438095-58af-4851-be8c-81c335fb0512"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_5"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ninacheza na Sokwe na twiga wangu milimani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SOKWE"," userResponse":" SOKWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685271901","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685271900"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" 09438095-58af-4851-be8c-81c335fb0512"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_5"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ninacheza na Sokwe na twiga wangu milimani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685272435","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685272434"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" 09438095-58af-4851-be8c-81c335fb0512"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_5"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ninacheza na Sokwe na twiga wangu milimani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TWIGA"," userResponse":" TWIGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685273150","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685273150"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" 09438095-58af-4851-be8c-81c335fb0512"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_5"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ninacheza na Sokwe na twiga wangu milimani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANGU"," userResponse":" WANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685273957","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685273956"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" 09438095-58af-4851-be8c-81c335fb0512"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_5"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ninacheza na Sokwe na twiga wangu milimani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MILIMANI"," userResponse":" MILIMANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685277040","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685277040"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" 09438095-58af-4851-be8c-81c335fb0512"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_5"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyani wangu na Kima wanaogopa Bwana Kobe kwa kila njia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYANI"," userResponse":" NYANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685277582","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685277582"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" 09438095-58af-4851-be8c-81c335fb0512"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_5"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyani wangu na Kima wanaogopa Bwana Kobe kwa kila njia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANGU"," userResponse":" WANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685278267","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685278266"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" 09438095-58af-4851-be8c-81c335fb0512"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_5"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyani wangu na Kima wanaogopa Bwana Kobe kwa kila njia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685278893","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685278893"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" 09438095-58af-4851-be8c-81c335fb0512"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_5"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyani wangu na Kima wanaogopa Bwana Kobe kwa kila njia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIMA"," userResponse":" KIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685280084","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685280084"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" 09438095-58af-4851-be8c-81c335fb0512"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_5"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyani wangu na Kima wanaogopa Bwana Kobe kwa kila njia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANAOGOPA"," userResponse":" WANAOGOPA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685280636","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685280635"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" 09438095-58af-4851-be8c-81c335fb0512"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_5"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyani wangu na Kima wanaogopa Bwana Kobe kwa kila njia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BWANA"," userResponse":" BWANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685281295","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685281293"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" 09438095-58af-4851-be8c-81c335fb0512"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_5"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyani wangu na Kima wanaogopa Bwana Kobe kwa kila njia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KOBE"," userResponse":" KOBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685281642","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685281641"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" 09438095-58af-4851-be8c-81c335fb0512"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_5"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyani wangu na Kima wanaogopa Bwana Kobe kwa kila njia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685282164","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685282163"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" 09438095-58af-4851-be8c-81c335fb0512"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_5"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyani wangu na Kima wanaogopa Bwana Kobe kwa kila njia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILA"," userResponse":" KILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685282710","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685282709"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" 09438095-58af-4851-be8c-81c335fb0512"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_5"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyani wangu na Kima wanaogopa Bwana Kobe kwa kila njia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJIA"," userResponse":" NJIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685285752","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685285751"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" 09438095-58af-4851-be8c-81c335fb0512"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_5"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na Kima wangu tunakula ndizi na Nyani kila siku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIMI"," userResponse":" MIMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685285981","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685285980"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" 09438095-58af-4851-be8c-81c335fb0512"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_5"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na Kima wangu tunakula ndizi na Nyani kila siku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685286565","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685286564"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" 09438095-58af-4851-be8c-81c335fb0512"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_5"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na Kima wangu tunakula ndizi na Nyani kila siku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIMA"," userResponse":" KIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685287087","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685287087"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" 09438095-58af-4851-be8c-81c335fb0512"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_5"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na Kima wangu tunakula ndizi na Nyani kila siku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANGU"," userResponse":" WANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685288537","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685288533"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" 09438095-58af-4851-be8c-81c335fb0512"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_5"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na Kima wangu tunakula ndizi na Nyani kila siku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUNAKULA"," userResponse":" TUNAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685289317","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685289315"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" 09438095-58af-4851-be8c-81c335fb0512"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_5"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na Kima wangu tunakula ndizi na Nyani kila siku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDIZI"," userResponse":" NDIZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685289716","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685289715"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" 09438095-58af-4851-be8c-81c335fb0512"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_5"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na Kima wangu tunakula ndizi na Nyani kila siku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685290316","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685290316"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" 09438095-58af-4851-be8c-81c335fb0512"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_5"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na Kima wangu tunakula ndizi na Nyani kila siku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYANI"," userResponse":" NYANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685290777","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685290777"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" 09438095-58af-4851-be8c-81c335fb0512"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_5"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na Kima wangu tunakula ndizi na Nyani kila siku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILA"," userResponse":" KILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685291436","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685291436"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" 09438095-58af-4851-be8c-81c335fb0512"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_5"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na Kima wangu tunakula ndizi na Nyani kila siku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685294429","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685294428"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" 09438095-58af-4851-be8c-81c335fb0512"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_5"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyani wangu na Kima wanaogopa Bwana Kobe kwa kila njia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYANI"," userResponse":" NYANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685294970","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685294969"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" 09438095-58af-4851-be8c-81c335fb0512"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_5"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyani wangu na Kima wanaogopa Bwana Kobe kwa kila njia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANGU"," userResponse":" WANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685295679","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685295679"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" 09438095-58af-4851-be8c-81c335fb0512"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_5"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyani wangu na Kima wanaogopa Bwana Kobe kwa kila njia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685296307","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685296307"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" 09438095-58af-4851-be8c-81c335fb0512"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_5"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyani wangu na Kima wanaogopa Bwana Kobe kwa kila njia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIMA"," userResponse":" KIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685297522","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685297521"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" 09438095-58af-4851-be8c-81c335fb0512"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_5"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyani wangu na Kima wanaogopa Bwana Kobe kwa kila njia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANAOGOPA"," userResponse":" WANAOGOPA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685298062","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685298061"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" 09438095-58af-4851-be8c-81c335fb0512"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_5"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyani wangu na Kima wanaogopa Bwana Kobe kwa kila njia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BWANA"," userResponse":" BWANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685298721","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685298720"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" 09438095-58af-4851-be8c-81c335fb0512"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_5"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyani wangu na Kima wanaogopa Bwana Kobe kwa kila njia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KOBE"," userResponse":" KOBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685299064","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685299063"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" 09438095-58af-4851-be8c-81c335fb0512"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_5"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyani wangu na Kima wanaogopa Bwana Kobe kwa kila njia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685299580","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685299580"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" 09438095-58af-4851-be8c-81c335fb0512"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_5"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyani wangu na Kima wanaogopa Bwana Kobe kwa kila njia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILA"," userResponse":" KILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685300124","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685300124"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" 09438095-58af-4851-be8c-81c335fb0512"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_5"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyani wangu na Kima wanaogopa Bwana Kobe kwa kila njia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJIA"," userResponse":" NJIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685303033","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685303028"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" 09438095-58af-4851-be8c-81c335fb0512"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_5"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kobe nami tunaenda nyumbani polepole na Bi Nyoka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BWANA"," userResponse":" BWANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685303609","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685303608"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" 09438095-58af-4851-be8c-81c335fb0512"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_5"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kobe nami tunaenda nyumbani polepole na Bi Nyoka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KOBE"," userResponse":" KOBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685304358","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685304358"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" 09438095-58af-4851-be8c-81c335fb0512"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_5"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kobe nami tunaenda nyumbani polepole na Bi Nyoka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAMI"," userResponse":" NAMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685305506","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685305505"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" 09438095-58af-4851-be8c-81c335fb0512"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_5"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kobe nami tunaenda nyumbani polepole na Bi Nyoka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUNAENDA"," userResponse":" TUNAENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685306292","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685306291"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" 09438095-58af-4851-be8c-81c335fb0512"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_5"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kobe nami tunaenda nyumbani polepole na Bi Nyoka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" NYUMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685307523","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685307523"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" 09438095-58af-4851-be8c-81c335fb0512"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_5"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kobe nami tunaenda nyumbani polepole na Bi Nyoka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" POLEPOLE"," userResponse":" POLEPOLE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685308096","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685308095"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" 09438095-58af-4851-be8c-81c335fb0512"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_5"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kobe nami tunaenda nyumbani polepole na Bi Nyoka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685308400","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685308399"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" 09438095-58af-4851-be8c-81c335fb0512"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_5"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kobe nami tunaenda nyumbani polepole na Bi Nyoka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BI"," userResponse":" BI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685308989","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685308989"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" 09438095-58af-4851-be8c-81c335fb0512"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_5"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kobe nami tunaenda nyumbani polepole na Bi Nyoka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYOKA"," userResponse":" NYOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685311496","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685311496"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" 09438095-58af-4851-be8c-81c335fb0512"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_5"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bi Nyoka nami twapenda kusonya na kuimba nyimbo kando ya ziwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BI"," userResponse":" BI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685312010","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685312009"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" 09438095-58af-4851-be8c-81c335fb0512"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_5"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bi Nyoka nami twapenda kusonya na kuimba nyimbo kando ya ziwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYOKA"," userResponse":" NYOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685312659","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685312659"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" 09438095-58af-4851-be8c-81c335fb0512"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_5"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bi Nyoka nami twapenda kusonya na kuimba nyimbo kando ya ziwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAMI"," userResponse":" NAMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685313543","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685313543"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" 09438095-58af-4851-be8c-81c335fb0512"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_5"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bi Nyoka nami twapenda kusonya na kuimba nyimbo kando ya ziwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TWAPENDA"," userResponse":" TWAPENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685314464","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685314464"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" 09438095-58af-4851-be8c-81c335fb0512"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_5"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bi Nyoka nami twapenda kusonya na kuimba nyimbo kando ya ziwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSONYA"," userResponse":" KUSONYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685315021","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685315020"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" 09438095-58af-4851-be8c-81c335fb0512"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_5"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bi Nyoka nami twapenda kusonya na kuimba nyimbo kando ya ziwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685315783","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685315782"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" 09438095-58af-4851-be8c-81c335fb0512"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_5"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bi Nyoka nami twapenda kusonya na kuimba nyimbo kando ya ziwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUIMBA"," userResponse":" KUIMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685316458","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685316457"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" 09438095-58af-4851-be8c-81c335fb0512"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_5"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bi Nyoka nami twapenda kusonya na kuimba nyimbo kando ya ziwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYIMBO"," userResponse":" NYIMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685317101","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685317101"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" 09438095-58af-4851-be8c-81c335fb0512"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_5"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bi Nyoka nami twapenda kusonya na kuimba nyimbo kando ya ziwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KANDO"," userResponse":" KANDO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685317347","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685317347"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" 09438095-58af-4851-be8c-81c335fb0512"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_5"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bi Nyoka nami twapenda kusonya na kuimba nyimbo kando ya ziwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685317919","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685317919"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" 09438095-58af-4851-be8c-81c335fb0512"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_5"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bi Nyoka nami twapenda kusonya na kuimba nyimbo kando ya ziwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZIWA"," userResponse":" ZIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685320975","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685320974"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" 09438095-58af-4851-be8c-81c335fb0512"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_5"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na familia yangu nzima tunaishi pamoja kwa furaha kubwa!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIMI"," userResponse":" MIMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685321226","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685321226"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" 09438095-58af-4851-be8c-81c335fb0512"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_5"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na familia yangu nzima tunaishi pamoja kwa furaha kubwa!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685321976","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685321976"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" 09438095-58af-4851-be8c-81c335fb0512"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_5"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na familia yangu nzima tunaishi pamoja kwa furaha kubwa!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FAMILIA"," userResponse":" FAMILIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685322620","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685322619"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" 09438095-58af-4851-be8c-81c335fb0512"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_5"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na familia yangu nzima tunaishi pamoja kwa furaha kubwa!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" YANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685323350","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685323350"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" 09438095-58af-4851-be8c-81c335fb0512"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_5"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na familia yangu nzima tunaishi pamoja kwa furaha kubwa!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NZIMA"," userResponse":" NZIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685324587","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685324586"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" 09438095-58af-4851-be8c-81c335fb0512"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_5"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na familia yangu nzima tunaishi pamoja kwa furaha kubwa!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUNAISHI"," userResponse":" TUNAISHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685325418","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685325418"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" 09438095-58af-4851-be8c-81c335fb0512"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_5"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na familia yangu nzima tunaishi pamoja kwa furaha kubwa!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAMOJA"," userResponse":" PAMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685325770","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685325770"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" 09438095-58af-4851-be8c-81c335fb0512"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_5"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na familia yangu nzima tunaishi pamoja kwa furaha kubwa!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685327105","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685327105"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" 09438095-58af-4851-be8c-81c335fb0512"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_5"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na familia yangu nzima tunaishi pamoja kwa furaha kubwa!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FURAHA"," userResponse":" FURAHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685327835","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685327835"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" 09438095-58af-4851-be8c-81c335fb0512"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_5"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na familia yangu nzima tunaishi pamoja kwa furaha kubwa!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUBWA"," userResponse":" KUBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685330509","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685330507"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" 09438095-58af-4851-be8c-81c335fb0512"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_5"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Mimi na familia yangu nzima tunaishi pamoja kwa furaha kubwa!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685330620","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685330620"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" 09438095-58af-4851-be8c-81c335fb0512"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_5"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na familia yangu nzima tunaishi pamoja kwa furaha kubwa!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUBWA"," userResponse":" KUBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.noShow.25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685336227","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685336227"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" 09438095-58af-4851-be8c-81c335fb0512"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_5"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mimi na familia yangu nzima tunaishi pamoja kwa furaha kubwa!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.12__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685341882","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685341882"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" 09438095-58af-4851-be8c-81c335fb0512"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_5"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mimi na familia yangu nzima tunaishi pamoja kwa furaha kubwa!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.noShow.25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685347299","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685347299"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" 09438095-58af-4851-be8c-81c335fb0512"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_5"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mimi na familia yangu nzima tunaishi pamoja kwa furaha kubwa!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.gen.hear::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685439980","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685439980"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" 09438095-58af-4851-be8c-81c335fb0512"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_5"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Mimi na familia yangu nzima tunaishi pamoja kwa furaha kubwa!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685440078","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685440078"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" 123f69fc-d77a-4f7b-a49a-611acf8c2211"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je una meno mangapi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANGAPI"," userResponse":" MANGAPI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.noShow.25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685447788","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685447787"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" 123f69fc-d77a-4f7b-a49a-611acf8c2211"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Je una meno mangapi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.12__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685463168","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685463168"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" abfe144f-18b0-49dc-a70b-511e0e8cfd51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.12__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_0_5-4-0"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.12__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685470704","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685470704"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" abfe144f-18b0-49dc-a70b-511e0e8cfd51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.12__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_1_5-6-1"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.12__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685478869","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685478869"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" abfe144f-18b0-49dc-a70b-511e0e8cfd51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.12__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_2_1-3-2"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.12__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685488552","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685488552"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" abfe144f-18b0-49dc-a70b-511e0e8cfd51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.12__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_8-2-3"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.12__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685496183","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685496183"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" abfe144f-18b0-49dc-a70b-511e0e8cfd51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.12__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_4_5-6-4"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.12__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685502729","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685502728"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" abfe144f-18b0-49dc-a70b-511e0e8cfd51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.12__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_5_0-9-5"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.12__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685508098","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685508098"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" abfe144f-18b0-49dc-a70b-511e0e8cfd51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.12__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_6_2-6-7"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.12__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685515148","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685515148"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" abfe144f-18b0-49dc-a70b-511e0e8cfd51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.12__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_9-7-8"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.12__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685521563","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685521563"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" abfe144f-18b0-49dc-a70b-511e0e8cfd51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.12__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_8_8-6-4"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.12__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685527535","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685527535"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" abfe144f-18b0-49dc-a70b-511e0e8cfd51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.12__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_8_8-6-4"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.12__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685532285","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685532285"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" abfe144f-18b0-49dc-a70b-511e0e8cfd51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.12__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_8_8-6-4"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.12__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685537408","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685537407"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" abfe144f-18b0-49dc-a70b-511e0e8cfd51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.12__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_9_4-9-1"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.12__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685543936","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685543936"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" abfe144f-18b0-49dc-a70b-511e0e8cfd51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.12__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_9_4-9-1"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.noShow.25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685552901","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685552901"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" 5561a0d7-5b83-4c8c-a208-096111e967f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.noShow.25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_A_U-E-A"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.noShow.25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685556376","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685556375"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" 5561a0d7-5b83-4c8c-a208-096111e967f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.noShow.25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_E_E-I-O"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.noShow.25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685559536","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685559536"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" 5561a0d7-5b83-4c8c-a208-096111e967f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.noShow.25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_I_I-U-E"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.noShow.25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685562583","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685562583"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" 5561a0d7-5b83-4c8c-a208-096111e967f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.noShow.25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_O_O-E-U"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.noShow.25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685565709","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685565709"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" 5561a0d7-5b83-4c8c-a208-096111e967f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.noShow.25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_U_U-E-O"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.noShow.25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685571503","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685571502"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" 5561a0d7-5b83-4c8c-a208-096111e967f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.noShow.25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_U_U-E-O"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.gen.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685581031","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685581031"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" 5561a0d7-5b83-4c8c-a208-096111e967f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.noShow.25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_U_U-E-O"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.gen.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685589746","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685589746"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" 5561a0d7-5b83-4c8c-a208-096111e967f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.noShow.25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_U_U-E-O"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.noShow.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685598733","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685598733"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" 0726048c-24c1-4ece-845d-a387975621ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.noShow.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_a_a-u-e"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.noShow.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685602534","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685602533"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" 0726048c-24c1-4ece-845d-a387975621ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.noShow.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_e_o-i-e"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.noShow.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685610170","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685610170"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" 0726048c-24c1-4ece-845d-a387975621ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.noShow.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_i_u-i-e"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.noShow.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685613946","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685613946"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" 0726048c-24c1-4ece-845d-a387975621ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.noShow.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_o_o-i-e"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.noShow.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685621789","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685621788"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" 0726048c-24c1-4ece-845d-a387975621ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.noShow.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_u_a-o-u"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.noShow.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685627574","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685627574"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" 0726048c-24c1-4ece-845d-a387975621ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.noShow.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_u_a-o-u"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685639204","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685639203"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" 142e3860-5fc5-4fd1-a90b-7e4d7f34a39d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kusoma kusoma"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSOMA"," userResponse":" KUSOMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685640215","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685640215"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" 142e3860-5fc5-4fd1-a90b-7e4d7f34a39d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kusoma kusoma"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSOMA"," userResponse":" KUSOMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685643153","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685643153"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" 142e3860-5fc5-4fd1-a90b-7e4d7f34a39d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunataka macho yaone"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNATAKA"," userResponse":" KUNATAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685643690","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685643690"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" 142e3860-5fc5-4fd1-a90b-7e4d7f34a39d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunataka macho yaone"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MACHO"," userResponse":" MACHO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685644348","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685644348"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" 142e3860-5fc5-4fd1-a90b-7e4d7f34a39d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunataka macho yaone"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAONE"," userResponse":" YAONE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685648506","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685648505"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" 142e3860-5fc5-4fd1-a90b-7e4d7f34a39d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Masikio yasikie"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MASIKIO"," userResponse":" MASIKIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685649448","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685649447"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" 142e3860-5fc5-4fd1-a90b-7e4d7f34a39d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Masikio yasikie"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YASIKIE"," userResponse":" YASIKIE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685653076","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685653076"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" 142e3860-5fc5-4fd1-a90b-7e4d7f34a39d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na mdomo useme"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685653869","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685653869"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" 142e3860-5fc5-4fd1-a90b-7e4d7f34a39d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na mdomo useme"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MDOMO"," userResponse":" MDOMO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685654849","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685654849"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" 142e3860-5fc5-4fd1-a90b-7e4d7f34a39d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na mdomo useme"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USEME"," userResponse":" USEME"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685658745","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685658745"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" 142e3860-5fc5-4fd1-a90b-7e4d7f34a39d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kusoma kusoma"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSOMA"," userResponse":" KUSOMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685659721","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685659721"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" 142e3860-5fc5-4fd1-a90b-7e4d7f34a39d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kusoma kusoma"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSOMA"," userResponse":" KUSOMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685662679","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685662677"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" 142e3860-5fc5-4fd1-a90b-7e4d7f34a39d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunataka macho yaone"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNATAKA"," userResponse":" KUNATAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685663220","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685663219"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" 142e3860-5fc5-4fd1-a90b-7e4d7f34a39d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunataka macho yaone"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MACHO"," userResponse":" MACHO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685663871","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685663871"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" 142e3860-5fc5-4fd1-a90b-7e4d7f34a39d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunataka macho yaone"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAONE"," userResponse":" YAONE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685668019","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685668019"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" 142e3860-5fc5-4fd1-a90b-7e4d7f34a39d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Masikio yasikie"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MASIKIO"," userResponse":" MASIKIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685668955","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685668955"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" 142e3860-5fc5-4fd1-a90b-7e4d7f34a39d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Masikio yasikie"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YASIKIE"," userResponse":" YASIKIE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685672646","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685672646"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" 142e3860-5fc5-4fd1-a90b-7e4d7f34a39d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na mdomo useme"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685673459","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685673457"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" 142e3860-5fc5-4fd1-a90b-7e4d7f34a39d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na mdomo useme"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MDOMO"," userResponse":" MDOMO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685674461","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685674460"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" 142e3860-5fc5-4fd1-a90b-7e4d7f34a39d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na mdomo useme"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USEME"," userResponse":" USEME"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685677769","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685677768"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" 142e3860-5fc5-4fd1-a90b-7e4d7f34a39d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Na mdomo useme"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685677878","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685677878"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_202456"," gameId":" 142e3860-5fc5-4fd1-a90b-7e4d7f34a39d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na mdomo useme"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USEME"," userResponse":" USEME"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}